A Guide to the Records of the Division of Motion Picture Censorship, 1926-1968
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence (Active Theaters and Drive-ins), 1957-1965
  - Pitts - Emporia, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 50, Folder 82)
  - Pitts Drive-In - Front Royal, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 50, Folder 83)
  - Pitts Drive-In - Manassas, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 50, Folder 84)
  - Pitts Theater - Manassas, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 50, Folder 85)
  - Pitts Drive-In - Fredericksburg, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 50, Folder 86)
  - Pitts Drive-In - Kilmarnock, Va., 1959-1964 (Box 50, Folder 87)
  - Pitts Drive-In - Orange, Va., 1961-1964 (Box 50, Folder 88)
  - Pitts - Warrenton, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 50, Folder 89)
  - Pitts Madison - Orange, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 50, Folder 90)
  - Pitts Park - Front Royal, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 50, Folder 91)
  - Plantation Drive-In - Suffolk, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 50, Folder 92)
  - Plaza - Winchester, Va., 1964-1965 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Pound - Pound, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Powell Valley - Big Stone Gap, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Pulaski - Pulaski, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Pulaski Drive-In - Dublin, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Radford - Radford, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Rapppanna - Urbanna, Va., 1957-1965 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Reed - Alexandria, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Regal - Norfolk, Va. (Negro), 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Rex - Galax, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Rex - Martinsville, Va., 1962-1964 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Rialto - Danville, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Richmond - Alexandria, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Ridge Drive-In - Charlottesville, Va., 1962-1964 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Riverside Drive-In - Roanoke, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Riverview - Norfolk, Va., 1961-1965 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Rives - Martinsville, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Rockbridge - Buena Vista, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Rosebowl - Ashland, Va., 1961-1965 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Roseland - Chancock, Va., 1961-1965 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Rosele - Norfolk, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Rosna - Norfolk, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Roth's Drive-In, Harrisonburg, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Roxy - Martinsville, Va., 1960-1963 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Royal Drive-In - Parksley, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Royal Drive-In - Winchester, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Ruckersville - Ruckersville, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Russell - Lebanon, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Salem - Salem, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Shenandoah Drive-In - Roanoke, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Shenandoah Drive-In - Woodstock, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Shore Drive-In - Bayside, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Sidney Lust Drive-In - Hampton, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Skyline Drive-In - Waynesboro, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Skyview Drive-In - Marion, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - South Drive-In - Norfolk, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Star City Drive-In - Roanoke, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Starlite Drive-In - Chatham, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Starlight Drive-In - Christiansburg, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Star Drive-In - Galax, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - StarVue Drive-In - Rocky Mount, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - State Theater - Clarksville, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - State Theater - Damascus, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - State Theater - Falls Church, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  - State Theater - Farmville, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  - State Theater - Harrisonburg, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - State Theater - Lexington, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  - State Theater - Portsmouth, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  - Staunton Drive-In - Staunton, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  - Stone - Bassett, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  - Strand - Covington, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  - Suburban - Norfolk, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Summit Drive-In - Glade Spring, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  - Sunset Drive-In - Alexandria, Va., 1961-1965 (Box 51, Folder 54)
  - Sunset Drive-In - Tazewell, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  - Sunset Drive-In - Wytheville, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  - Super 17 Drive-In - Portsmouth, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Super 29 Drive-In - Fairfax, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 58)
  - Talley's Drive-In - Louisa, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 59)
  - Tally Ho - Leesburg, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Taylor - Gate City, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 61)
  - Taylor - Gate City, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 62)
  - 360 Drive-In - Danville, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 63)
  - Tidewater - Hayes, Va., 1961-1965 (Box 51, Folder 64)
  - Town Theater - Norfolk, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 65)
  - Towne Theater - Hillsville, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 66)
  - Trail - Big Stone Gap, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 67)
  - Trail Drive-In - Roanoke, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 68)
  - Triangle Drive-In - Triangle, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 69)
  - Tri-County Drive-In - Clarkston, Va., 1961-1965 (Box 51, Folder 70)
  - Twi-Light Drive-In - Front Royal, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 71)
  - Twin Pines - Richmond, Va., 1959 (Box 51, Folder 72)
  - University - Charlottesville, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 73)
  - Van Sant Drive-In - Van Sant, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 74)
  - Vernon - Alexandria, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 75)
  - Vest Drive-In - Copperhill/Galay, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 76)
  - Vienna - Vienna, Va., 1964-1965 (Box 51, Folder 77)
  - Victoria - Fredericksburg, Va., 1959-1965 (Box 51, Folder 78)
  - Village - Newport News, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 79)
  - Virginia Theater - Alexandria, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 80)
  - Virginia Theater - Harrisonburg, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 81)
  - Virginia Theater - Roanoke, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 82)
  - Virginia Beach Drive-In - Virginia Beach, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 83)
  - Vista Theater - Altavista, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 84)
  - Vista Drive-In - Altavista, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 51, Folder 85)
  - Visulite - Covington, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 86)
  - Visulite Theater - Staunton, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 87)
  - Warner - Lynchburg, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 88)
  - Warwick - Newport News, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 89)
  - Wayne - Waynesboro, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 51, Folder 90)
  - Willard - Norfolk, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Williamsburg - Williamsburg, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Wilson - Arlington, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Winchester Drive-In - Winchester, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Wythe - Hampton, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Zephyr - Abingdon, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Correspondence (Inactive, closed theaters), 1957-1965
  This series offers the outgoing and incoming letters between the Director of the Division of Motion Picture Censorship and the owners of theaters and drive-ins that were no longer in existence. The correspondence mainly consists of inquiries by the Director for the name of inspectors for the theaters and notification to the Director that the theater or drive-in is no longer in operation. Some files may contain returned admission cards issued to inspectors for their free admittance into the theaters. These files include index cards with the name and address of the inspector assigned to a specific theater.
  - Abingdon Theatre - Gloucester, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Academy Theatre - Lynchburg, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Afton - Portsmouth, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Airport Drive-in - Arlington, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Alamo - Grundy, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Alberta Theatre - Alberta, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Alta Drive-in - Alta Vista, Va., 1958-1958 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Anchor Drive-in - Warwick, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Appalachian - Appalachia, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Ashland - Hanover, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Asta - Maryus, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Auditorium - Cary's Brook, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Austinville Drive-in - Austinville, Va., 1956-1958 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Bagley Drive-in - Kenbridge, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Barney - Petersburg, Va. (Negro), 1960-1962 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Basie - Hampton, Va. (Negro), 1957-1962 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Beacon Drive-in - Bristol, Va., 1958-1959 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Bellvue - Richmond, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Berkeley - Norfolk, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Bland - Portsmouth, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Bluegrass - St. Paul, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Blueridge - Elkton, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - Booker T. or Carver Theatre - Norfolk, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - Booker T. - Roanoke, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - Boykins - Boykins, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - Bridge - Bedford, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - Bridge - Luray, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - Broadway - Hopewell, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  - Brookneal - Brookneal, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  - Bruton - Williamsburg, Va. (Negro), 1958 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  - Bruton Heights - Williamsburg, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  - Burkeville - Burkeville, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  - Cab Theater - Ashland, Va. (Negro), 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  - Callaghan Drive-in - Covington, Va., 1960-1962 (Box 52, Folder 40)
  - Cameo - Exmore, Va., 1957 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  - Capitol - Winchester, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  - Carver - Alexandria, Va. (Negro), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - Carver - Cape Charles, Va., 1958-1959 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - Carver - Portsmouth, Va. (Negro), 1958 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  - Carver - Suffolk, Va. (Negro), 1960-1963 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  - Cary's Brook Theater - Fork Union, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 47)
  - Castle Theater - Fincastle, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 48)
  - Cavalier - Suffolk, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 49)
  - Center - Centerville, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 50)
  - Center - Hampton, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 51)
  - Central - Coeburn, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 52)
  - Central Star - Madison, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 53)
  - Chadwick - Suffolk, Va., 1960-1963 (Box 52, Folder 54)
  - Chase City Drive-in - Chase City, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 55)
  - Clarco - Berryville, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 56)
  - Clarksvile - Clarksville, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 57)
  - Clincho - Clincho, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 58)
  - Clover - Clover, Va., 1958-1961 (Box 52, Folder 59)
  - Colonial - Galax, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 60)
  - Colonial - Salem, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 61)
  - Community Theater - Schuyler, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 62)
  - Cradock - Portsmouth, Va., 1957 (Box 52, Folder 63)
  - Crozet - Crozet, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 64)
  - Crozet Drive-in - Crewe, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 65)
  - Crozet Drive-in - Crozet, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 66)
  - Dillwyn - Dillwyn, Va., 1957-1963 (Box 52, Folder 67)
  - Eagle - Big Stone Gap, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 68)
  - Edge Hill - Gloucester, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 69)
  - Elco - Portsmouth, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 52, Folder 70)
  - Elk Creek - Elk Creek, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 52, Folder 71)
  - Fairview - Dillwyn, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 72)
  - Family Drive-in - Bassett, Va., 1959 (Box 52, Folder 73)
  - 501 Drive-in - Halifax, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 74)
  - Floyd - Floyd, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 75)
  - Floyd Willis - Floyd, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 76)
  - Fort Early - Lynchburg, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 77)
  - Fort Hell Drive-in - Petersburg, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 78)
  - Friendly Drive-in - Bassett, Va., 1957-1961 (Box 52, Folder 79)
  - Fries Theater - Fries, Va., 1958-1963 (Box 52, Folder 80)
  - Gate City - Gate City, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 81)
  - Gates - Portsmouth, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 82)
  - Green Acres - Newport News, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 83)
  - Gretna - Gretna, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 52, Folder 84)
  - Grottoes - Grottoes, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 85)
  - Hanover - Hanover, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 86)
  - Harrison - Lynchburg, Va., 1959-1961 (Box 52, Folder 87)
  - Haysi - Haysi, Va., 1957-1963 (Box 52, Folder 88)
  - Henrico Theater - Highland Springs, Va., 1957-1961 (Box 52, Folder 89)
  - Herndon - Herndon, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 52, Folder 90)
  - Hollywood Theater - Middleburg, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 91)
  - Hunter's Lodge Drive-in - Troy, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 52, Folder 92)
  - Idle Hour Theater - Petersburg, Va. (Negro), 1958-1962 (Box 52, Folder 93)
  - Keith's Drive-in - Coeburn, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 94)
  - Kenbridge - Kenbridge, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 95)
  - Keokee Theater - Keokee, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 96)
  - Kilmarnock Drive-in - Kilmarnock, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 97)
  - Lafayette - Charlottesville, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 98)
  - Laurel Drive-in - Dante, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 99)
  - Lea Theater - Appomattox, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 100)
  - Lea Theater - Danville, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 52, Folder 101)
  - Lee - Bluefield, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 102)
  - Lee - Farmville, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 103)
  - Lee - Hampton, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 52, Folder 104)
  - Lee - White Stone, Va., 1958-1959 (Box 52, Folder 105)
  - Lee Drive-in - Lexington, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 106)
  - Lee Hi-Way Drive-in - Falls Church, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 107)
  - Liberty - Bedford, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 108)
  - Little Theater - Blacksburg, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 109)
  - Loch Haven - Roanoke, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 110)
  - Lonesome Pine Drive-in - Coeburn, Va., 1961-1964 (Box 52, Folder 111)
  - Lust Drive-in - Hampton, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 112)
  - Lyric Theater - Portsmouth, Va. (Negro), 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 113)
  - Madison Drive-in - Madison, Va., 1962 (Box 52, Folder 114)
  - Mallie Theater - Bird Nest, Va. (Negro), 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 115)
  - Manassas Drive-in - Manassas, Va., 1959 (Box 52, Folder 116)
  - Mecca - Chase City, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 52, Folder 117)
  - Midway - Christiansburg, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 118)
  - Midway - Galax, Va., 1957-1961 (Box 52, Folder 119)
  - Midway - Warner, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 120)
  - Midway - Radford, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 121)
  - Monteray Theater - Monteray, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 122)
  - Montross - Montross, Va., 1961-1964 (Box 52, Folder 123)
  - Moonlite Drive-in - South Boston, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 124)
  - Mountain View Drive-in - Buena Vista, Va., 1953 (Box 52, Folder 125)
  - Narrows Theater - Narrrows, Va., 1951-1958 (Box 52, Folder 126)
  - Nelson - Mt. Jackson, Va., 1958-1963 (Box 52, Folder 127)
  - New Theater - Chincoteague, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 128)
  - New Theater - Exmore, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 129)
  - New Theater - Keysville, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 130)
  - New Coeburn - Coeburn, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 131)
  - New Dixie - Staunton, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 132)
  - New Powell - Chincoteague, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 133)
  - New Rex - Norfolk, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 134)
  - North Theater - Danville, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 52, Folder 135)
  - Norview - Norfolk, Va., 1958-1962 (Box 52, Folder 136)
  - Oakwood Drive-in - Virgilina, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 137)
  - Open Air Theater (Negro) - Petersburg, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 138)
  - Orange Drive-in - Orange, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 139)
  - Palace Theater - Winchester, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 140)
  - Parish Hall - McLean, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 141)
  - Park Theater - Front Royal, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 142)
  - Park Theater - Norfolk, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 143)
  - Park Theater - Roanoke, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 144)
  - Park Drive-in - Clifton Forge, Va., 1959-1964 (Box 52, Folder 145)
  - Patrick Drive-in - Stuart, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 146)
  - Penn - Independence, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 147)
  - Petersburg Drive-in - Petersburg, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 148)
  - Pitts Colonial - Fredericksburg, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 149)
  - Pitts Drive-in - Lawrenceville, Va., 1957 (Box 52, Folder 150)
  - Pitts Fairfax - Culpeper, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 151)
  - Pitts Murphy - Front Royal, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 152)
  - Pitts Victoria - Fredericksburg, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 153)
  - Pix - Rose Hill, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 154)
  - Princess Anne - Norfolk, Va., 1958-1965 (Box 52, Folder 155)
  - Princess Theater - South Boston, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 156)
  - Purceyville - Purceyville, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 157)
  - Radium - Cape Charles, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 52, Folder 158)
  - Rainbow Drive-in - Pennington Gap, Va., n.d. (Box 52, Folder 159)
  - Rainbow - St. Charles, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 160)
  - Rainbow - Woodway, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 52, Folder 161)
  - Randolph - Halifax, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 162)
  - Raven - Raven, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 163)
  - Reed - Berryville, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 164)
  - Regent - Colonial Heights, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 165)
  - Rex - Keen Mountain, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 166)
  - Rex - Norfolk, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 167)
  - Rex - Page, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 168)
  - Rex - Petersburg, Va., 1959-1960 (Box 52, Folder 169)
  - Rim - Hayes, Va. (Negro), 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 170)
  - Rio - Norfolk, Va. (Negro), 1958-1960 (Box 52, Folder 171)
  - Ritz - Danville, Va. (Negro), 1957-1960 (Box 52, Folder 172)
  - Ritz - Norfolk, Va. (Negro), 1958-1962 (Box 52, Folder 173)
  - Roanoke - Roanoke, Va., 1957-1961 (Box 52, Folder 174)
  - Rose Bowl Drive-in - Hanover, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 175)
  - Roth's Drive-in - Grottoes, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 52, Folder 176)
  - Roxy - Norfolk, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 52, Folder 177)
  - Royal - Norfolk, Va. (Negro), 1958 (Box 52, Folder 178)
  - Ruckersville Drive-in - Ruckersville, Va., 1958 (Box 52, Folder 179)
  - Salt Theater - Saltville, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 52, Folder 180)
  - Schoolfield - Danville, Va., 1958-1961 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Schoolfield - Schoolfield, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Schuyler - Saltville, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Shelby - Bristol, Va., 1958-1962 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Shenandoah - Shenandoah, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Shenandoah Valley - Edinburg, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Shirlington Theater - Arlington, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Skyvue - Stuart, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Smithfield - Smithfield, Va., 1957-1961 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Stanley - Stanley, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Star - Richlands, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Star - South Hill, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Star - Stuart, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Starlite - Clintwood, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Starlite - Hurley, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - State Theater - Appalachia, Va., 1957-1963 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - State Theater - Bristol, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - State Theater - Lawrenceville, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - State Theater - Petersburg, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - State Theater - Radford, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Stevensville - Lexington, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Stockade Drive-in (Negro) - Williamsburg, Va., 1960-1964 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Strand - Harrisonburg, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Strand - Staunton, Va., 1957-1961 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Strasburg - Strasburg, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Sundown Drive-in - Gate City, Va., 1957-1962 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Talley - Louisa, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Triangle - Quantico, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Turner's Station - St. Charles, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Uptown - Woodstock, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Valley Theater - Edinburg, Va., 1957-1961 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Valley, - Jewel Valley, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Valley, - Tazewell, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Van Sant, - Grundy, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Victoria, - Victoria, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Village - Glade Springs, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Theater - Radford, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Virginian - St. Charles, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Wakefield - Wakefield, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Wardley - Callao, Va., 1960-1963 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Warner - Monterey, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Warsaw - Warsaw, Va., 1958-1960 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Wells - Norfolk, Va., 1957-1959 (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - West Point - West Point, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Wicomico - Gloucester Point, Va., 1958-1959 (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Wilder - Norfolk, Va., 1960-1965 (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Wise Open Air - Wise, Va., 1957-1963 (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - Wythe Theater - Newport News, Va., 1958 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Wythe - Wytheville, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - York - West Point, Va., 1957-1960 (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - York Drive-in - Yorktown, Va., 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 51)
- General correspondence and controversial films, 1922-1966
  This series combines general correspondence of the agency director and correspondence regarding films that were eliminated for viewing within the state of Virginia. The correspondence consists of letters mailed to movie distributors and court documents, as well as correspondence from the state's Attorney General. The series also includes selected promotional movie posters, examples of advertisements in movie industry trade magazines, and scripts of some of the movies listed.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - A, 1960 (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - After Bed Time, 1923 (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - And God Created Woman, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Appeal Cases (see Procedures), 1963 (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - Attorney General, 1957-1960 (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - B, 1960-1961 (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - Baby Face, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Band of Angels (see transcript, Box 57, folder 7, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - Because of Eve, 1951-1957 (Box 53, Folder 60)
  - Bed of Grass, 1957-1958 (Box 53, Folder 61)
  - B-Girl Rhapsody, 1956 (Box 53, Folder 62)
  - Bicycle Theif, 1950 (Box 53, Folder 63)
  - Bill - HB 176, Jan. 26, 1966, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 64)
  - Bill - other censor board fees, some annual reports, 1957-1962 (Box 53, Folder 65)
  - Birth of a Baby, 1939 (Box 53, Folder 66)
  - Birth of a Nation, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 67)
  - Birthright - Unlawful Exhibition, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 68)
  - Black Like Me, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 69)
  - Blackboard Jungle, 1955 (Box 53, Folder 70)
  - Blood Feast, 1964-1965 (Box 53, Folder 71)
  - Bond Surety, 1957-1964 (Box 53, Folder 72)
  - Box Office Attractions, Inc., 1964-1965 (Box 53, Folder 73)
  - Burlesque in Harlem, 1951-1952 (Box 53, Folder 74)
  - Burning Cross, The, 1947 (Box 53, Folder 75)
  - C, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 76)
  - Can Can Follies, 1955-1957 (Box 53, Folder 77)
  - Career Girls on a Naked Holiday, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 78)
  - Censorship - documentary, 1962 (Box 53, Folder 79)
  - Censorship - newsclippings, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 80)
  - Certifying papers to the Court of Appeals, 1958-1963 (Box 53, Folder 81)
  - Childred of the Sun, 1934 (Box 53, Folder 82)
  - Childrens' Hour, The, 1961 (Box 53, Folder 83)